[{"answer": "Lopped off", "docId": "sleepy-hollow_shooting.txt", "asentId": 3, "question": "I have never been allowed to put them to the test", "qsentId": 2}, {"answer": "Only that the three were slain in open ground and their heads found severed from their bodies..", "docId": "sleepy-hollow_shooting.txt", "asentId": 5, "question": "The heads are ", "qsentId": 4}, {"answer": "You will see him too if he comes again.  The men of the village are posted to watch for him", "docId": "sleepy-hollow_shooting.txt", "asentId": 7, "question": "You are a long way from that place, sir", "qsentId": 6}, {"answer": " Then you have nothing to teach me", "docId": "sleepy-hollow_shooting.txt", "asentId": 9, "question": "Not everyone here believes it is the Horseman", "qsentId": 8}, {"answer": "And... the head... ", "docId": "sleepy-hollow_shooting.txt", "asentId": 11, "question": "Taken", "qsentId": 10}, {"answer": "I see", "docId": "sleepy-hollow_shooting.txt", "asentId": 13, "question": "Given by the dead my friend", "qsentId": 12}, {"answer": " -- to protect the rights of her child.  I was bound by my oath of office to keep the secret", "docId": "sleepy-hollow_shooting.txt", "asentId": 15, "question": " The Horseman killed her! ", "qsentId": 14}, {"answer": "You must not excite yourself", "docId": "sleepy-hollow_shooting.txt", "asentId": 17, "question": "Of course it was", "qsentId": 16}, {"answer": " We had no dealings with the magistrate that I know of..", "docId": "sleepy-hollow_shooting.txt", "asentId": 19, "question": " Everyone knew Widow my friend", "qsentId": 18}, {"answer": "I heard someone leaving last night. Looked like they headed to town, but I lost them in the woods", "docId": "sleepy-hollow_shooting.txt", "asentId": 21, "question": "All I saw was their lantern", "qsentId": 20}, {"answer": " A brick through your window is not what puts you in terror, Hardenbrook ... there is something else... I saw your fear, and my friend's and the doctor's, when you met at my friend's house... my friend paid with his head, and you fear for your own", "docId": "sleepy-hollow_shooting.txt", "asentId": 23, "question": "Drawn in by whom?", "qsentId": 22}, {"answer": "Drawn in by whom?", "docId": "sleepy-hollow_shooting.txt", "asentId": 25, "question": "No harm to come to whom", "qsentId": 24}, {"answer": "No harm to come to whom", "docId": "sleepy-hollow_shooting.txt", "asentId": 27, "question": "Made ?! ", "qsentId": 26}, {"answer": "Well... perhaps", "docId": "sleepy-hollow_shooting.txt", "asentId": 29, "question": " Your father... ", "qsentId": 28}, {"answer": " The Evil Eye", "docId": "sleepy-hollow_shooting.txt", "asentId": 31, "question": "It is someone casting spells against you", "qsentId": 30}, {"answer": "If you knew my father you would not have such harsh thoughts about him", "docId": "sleepy-hollow_shooting.txt", "asentId": 33, "question": "You are the Constable, not I", "qsentId": 32}]